抓住壁炉两侧  固定好位置
Okay, now holding sides of hearth in position,
将壁炉台组合至壁炉上方
lower mantelpiece assembly onto top tabs.
你看  我靠着自己这双手造了个壁炉呢
Look at that, I built a fireplace with my own two hands.
你好龙精虎猛哦
You're so butch.
哎哟  被纸割伤手了
Aw, I got a little paper cut.
完全不意外
Of course you did.
你的芊芊玉手比小牛肉还嫩呢
Your hands are softer than veal.
趁我没忘  提醒你一下  这周六
Oh, before I forget, Saturday I'm planning a little
桌上角色扮演游戏
我约了大家玩《龙与地下城》哦
Dungeons and Dragons night with the guys.
真的吗  周六晚你就打算这么庆祝啊
Really? That's how you're gonna spend your Saturday night?
别这样  我几乎都没什么机会玩了
Oh, come on, I hardly ever get a chance to play anymore.
你个可怜的娃
Oh, you poor thing.
有个真实存在还能滚床单的女朋友
Is having a real-life girlfriend who has sex with you
碍着你跟你心爱的小桌游嬉戏了吗
getting in the way of your board games?
是有一点啦
Little bit, yeah.
好耶  我一直都想玩玩看《龙与地下城》呢
Oh, great! I've always wanted to play Dungeons and Dragons.
抱歉  是我不好
Yeah, oh, I'm sorry.
我应该先说在前头
I should've mentioned this earlier.
你未被邀请
You're not invited.
为什么没有啊
Why not?
艾米  每隔一段时间
Amy, from time to time,
我们男人都需要挣脱文明礼仪的束缚
we men need to break free from the shackles of civility
并回归原始野性的自我
and get in touch with our primal animalistic selves.
就掷掷骰子
By rolling dice
然后用小人偶玩幻想游戏也算啊
and playing make-believe with little figurines?
是啊  又野蛮又粗暴啊
Yeah, like a bunch of savages.
周六晚啊
Saturday night?
我这周天天都加班
But I've been working late all week.
还想着那晚能是二人时光呢
That was gonna be our night.
我不去不行啊
But I have to go.
我们大家要一起玩啊
We play as a group.
要是我去不成  其他人会说你坏话的
If-if I'm not there, then everyone will blame you.
他们就会说  "伯纳黛特超扫兴
They'll be all, "Bernadette ruined everything.
她个臭八婆"
She's the worst."
你理解吗
So, you see?
我不能不去玩《龙与地下城》啊
I have to play Dungeons and Dragons...
是为我们婚姻着想
for the marriage.
你个死白痴
You're an idiot.
是你的小白痴
I'm your idiot.
死都甩不掉哦
Forever.
听我说  我们之前的确是说了
So, listen, I know we talked about
要去银湖吃吃东西
getting a bite to eat in Silver Lake,
然后去格里菲斯公园看看圣诞灯饰
and then seeing the Christmas lights in Griffith Park,
可莱纳德找我们去他家玩《龙与地下城》呢
but Leonard's talking about a big D and D game at his place.
周六夜要从嗨翻升级成史诗级啦
Saturday night just went from crazy to epic!
生活大爆炸 第六季  第十一集
谢尔顿  要想开始征途
All right, Sheldon, to start our quest,
你必须先打开我送你的这圣诞礼物
you need to open this little Christmas gift I got you.
圣诞礼物啊
A Christmas gift?
你明知道我不爱圣诞节
You know I don't enjoy Christmas.
圣诞节有什么不好啊
What's wrong with Christmas?
太多缺点  不知从何开始
Oh, where to begin?
室内摆树
Trees indoors.
猛拽古文  例如"此乃"圣诞佳节
Overuse of the words "'tis" and "'twas."
还有这荒谬的单脚袜习俗
And the absurd custom of one stocking.
是人都知道  袜子就该成双成对
Everyone knows socks belong in pairs.
谁会要单脚袜啊
Who uses one sock?
一只脚是木制假腿的海盗吧
Pirate with a peg leg?
有用处我就舒服多了  谢啦
Actually that helps, thank you.
就赶紧看里面有啥嘛
Would you just look inside?
是个卷轴
Oh, a scroll.
我最爱卷轴了
I like scrolls.
卷轴是我第三喜爱的
They're my third favorite system of
文字传输方式
transmitting the written word.
仅在石碑与飞机空中文字之后
After stone tablets and skywriting.
"在座各位皆是被召唤来参与
"You have all been summoned to join
紧张刺激的《龙与地下城》冒险的人选
a thrilling Dungeons and Dragons adventure.
你们踏上征途的起因
Your quest begins in
是由于一个神秘的北方小精灵村庄
a secret northern village of elves
被人血洗屠村"
who have all been massacred."
这故事走向我喜欢
I like where this is heading.
"你们的任务是要营救
"Your task is to rescue their leader
被困于食人魔地下城的村长"
from a dungeon of ogres."
好妙的故事转折啊
Oh, that's a saucy twist.
"而村长的名字是...
"That leader's name:
圣诞老人"
Santa Claus""
不  不  不啊
No, no, no!
圣诞老人是"呵  呵  呵"的笑
It's actually, "Ho, ho, ho,"
你再多练练就会了
but you'll get the hang of it.
我觉得把节日混合入任务里
Thought it'd be fun to make
会很有意思嘛
a quest with a holiday theme.
有意思吗
Fun?
把《龙与地下城》跟圣诞节混合起来
Mixing Dungeons and Dragons with Christmas is
就像是做三明治  把最好吃的果冻
like making a sandwich of grape jelly,
葡萄果冻
the best-tasting jelly,
跟最难吃的果冻  石化制果冻混一起
and petroleum jelly, the worst-tasting jelly.
石化制胶状物  直译石化制果冻  也就是凡士林]
好了  开始啦
Okay, here we go.
"你们发现自己
"You find yourselves
身处于圣诞村烟雾弥漫的废墟之中
in the smoking remains of Santa's village.
显然  此地刚发生过一场大战"
Clearly, a great battle has taken place."
好兴奋啊  第一个怪物露头
Oh, man, the first monster I see,
我要潜到他背后  掏出我的小魔棒
I'm gonna sneak up behind him, whip out my wand,
用我的魔法射满他菊花
and shoot my magic all over his ass.
你说出这些话时  自己有听到吗
Do you hear yourself when you say these things?
在雪地上发现了食人魔足印
Okay, there are ogre tracks and a trail of
还有用拐杖糖碎块留下的路线线索
broken candy canes in the snow.
谢尔顿  你采取什么行动
Sheldon, what do you do?
我选择这你残酷  没人性
I signal my contempt for your cruel plan
硬逼我庆祝圣诞节计划
to shove Christmas joy down my throat
以"你们瞧这二货"的言语来加以鄙视
by making a gesture that says, "get a load of this guy."
行  霍华德  你采取什么行动
Fine. Howard, what do you do?
我选择跟随食人魔足印
I follow the ogre tracks,
并在跟踪时  检查路上有无暗门密道
checking for secret doors along the way.
你发现了一个门后是阴暗走廊的暗门
And you discover a secret door leading to a dark corridor.
兄弟们  先布置好计划
Okay, guys, let's make a plan:
战士走前排  法师站后排
spell casters in the back, warriors in the front...
少废话  老子要杀进去了
No, screw that noise, I'm going in.
圣诞老人  撑着点  我来救你了
Hang on, Santa, I'm coming for you!
你跑进了一件兵器房里
Okay, you run into a room full of weapons,
触发了陷阱
hit a trip wire...
一门大炮炸飞了你的头  角色死亡  你出局了
...a cannon blows your face off, you die, you're out of the game.
等等  一门大炮啊
But... a canon?
我真的出局了吗
Am I really out of the game?
你真幸运
Lucky.
好了  游戏继续进行
Okay, come on, moving on.
等等  你们身上都没有复活之棒吗
Wait, doesn't anyone have a rod of resurrection?
你们谁有  我急需这跟小棒棒啊
Because if you've got one, I need it bad.
赶紧掏出你的棒棒  给人家来一棒嘛
Get in here with your rod and give it to me.
好吧  你说话之前
Okay, you need to say these things
得把原话在脑子里好好过一遍
in your head before you say them out loud.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
我不是故意打断你们的小游戏
I don't mean to interrupt your little game,
但我觉得你们会想知道  自己都错过了啥
but I thought you'd like to see what you're missing out on.
那么...
So...
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?
伯纳黛特脚踩豹纹高跟鞋
Bernadette's wearing leopard-print pumps
身穿爆乳红裙  均购自"永远21"
and a rack-tastic red dress from Forever 21.
接下来是艾米
And there's Amy,
与她的露"脚踝"装
showing all kinds of ankle.
身上那件衣服  我估计是购自"永远63"吧
In an outfit I'm assuming is from Forever 63.
而我自己呢...
And I, myself...
穿着一条小码紧身裙  我可是靠它
...am wearing a little number that got me
免了两张超速罚单和陪审员的义务
out of two speeding tickets and jury duty.
我知道她们是用夸张手法来表达某事
I know they're making a rhetorical point,
可我真看不出是说什么事
I just don't know what it is.
再见  伙计们  我们要去喝酒啦
See you, boys. We are going drinking.
等等  我能跟你们一起去吗
Uh, wait, can I come with you?
我玩的角色死了
My character died.
抱歉  拉杰  今晚是闺蜜之夜
Sorry, Raj, it's girls' night out.
或许下次吧
Maybe another time.
好吧
Okay...
走吧
Come on.
闺蜜之夜  闺蜜之夜
Girls' night, girls' night!
他怎么会听不到自己说这种话呢
How does he not hear that?
有什么大计
So, what's the plan?
我们要不要给各自的男友一点教训
Are we gonna teach our fellas a lesson
喝个酩酊大醉
by getting stinking drunk,
勾引陌生男人到厕所
luring strange men into the bathroom,
把厕所隔间变成性爱感官神殿
and turning the toilet stall into a temple of the senses?
-不要  -当然不
- No! - No!
天啊  现在谁才是"永远63"啊
Geez, who's Forever 63 now?
能给我们桌再来一瓶香槟吗
Can we get another bottle of champagne for the table?
别担心
Don't worry.
我请客
It's my treat.
谢谢
Thanks.
你应该多来参加我们的闺蜜之夜
You should come to girls' night more often.
绝不是因为如果你不在
And not just because if you weren't here,
我们就要从喝香槟沦落为喝啤酒哦
this would be a can of Pabst.
这是我的荣幸  能有机会宠溺女人
My pleasure; nothing makes me happier
比任何事都让我开心
than the chance to spoil a lady.
不信问问我的狗
Just ask my dog.
兽医说如果我再喂她鹅肝酱
My vet says if I give her any more foie gras,
她就要死于痛风了
she's going to die of gout.
常吃动物类内脏会导致尿酸高  从而引起痛风
我们今晚帮拉杰找个姑娘吧
Hey, let's help Raj meet a girl tonight.
别了别了  我无所谓
No, no, no, I'm fine.
慢着  我们说的是找个姑娘搞一夜情
Okay, wait, are we talking one-night stand
还是找个姑娘谈恋爱呀
or do we want to get him into a relationship?
找个姑娘把床上
Let's get him laid!
别这样  闺蜜之夜  主角是闺蜜
Stop it. You're ruining girls' night.
拉杰  你是个好男人
Raj, you're a great guy,
而且这酒吧全是单身女人  让我们帮你吧
you're in a bar full of single women; let us help you.
对啊  你真的是个好对象
Yeah, you're a real catch.
我知道你害羞  但这并不意味着
I know you're shy, but that doesn't mean
你生命中不应拥有一位佳人
you shouldn't have someone wonderful in your life.
你们真好心
That's sweet of you.
但你们能怎么帮我呢
But what can you do to help?
我们四周打探一下
We'll nose around,
看看能不能找到一个不错的姑娘  然后介绍你认识
see if we can find a nice girl, and then introduce you.
好吧
Okay.
有几点要注意
Well, a couple of things.
别告诉她们我出身富庶
Don't tell them I come from money.
我要她们爱我  而不是爱我的钱
I want them to love me for me.
她们一定要超级性感
They must be insanely hot.
身材样貌起码得有9分或10分
Like, nines or tens.
9分或10分吗
Nines or tens?
好吧  8分也可以接受
Okay, an eight is acceptable
前提是她会带另外一个8分女来跟我三人泡澡
if she's willing to bring another eight to the hot tub.
反正  我们找着啥样的你都会要  对吧
Bottom line: you'll take any woman who'll have you, right?
果断会要
In a New Delhi minute.
我不记得你在我店里买过这些小模型啊
I don't remember you buying these miniatures in my store.
是没买过
Oh, uh, yeah.
这是在亚马逊上买的
I got 'em on Amazon.
当然  我懂的
Sure. I get it.
与其扶持一个朋友
Why support a friend
为何不去扶持一家把你朋友的生活
when you can support a multinational conglomerate
挤压得穷苦潦倒的跨国大企业呢
that is crushing the life out of that friend?
我知道  但当我上网购物时
I know, but when I shop online,
我可以边上厕所边买
I can do it on the toilet.
你见过我的店吗
Have you seen my store?
那个地方跟厕所没两样
The whole place is a toilet.
能继续进行游戏了吗
C-Can we please move this along?
可以  抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
你们走到了的尽头
Uh, you come to the end of the tunnel
发现了一个大宝箱[大胸]
and find a large chest.
你将采取什么行动
What do you do?
对了  霍华德  拜托不要说
And, Howard, do not say,
"我要上去抓一把"
"I feel up the large chest."
不好意思  我现在可是已婚男人
Excuse me, I'm a married man now.
我才不会说这么幼稚的话呢
I wasn't going to say anything so juvenile.
很好  那你会怎么做
Great. What do you do?
我会走到那个大胸[大宝箱]前
I walk up to the large chest,
把我的脸埋进去  然后这样玩
bury my face in it and go.
-我选择打开宝箱  -锁着呢
- I open the chest. - It's locked,
但你身后的门突然砰一声关上
but suddenly the door behind you slams shut
现在房间两侧的墙壁开始往中间逼近
and now the walls of the room start closing in.
这下惨了
That's not good.
我和我的角色都有幽闭恐惧症
My character and I both have claustrophobia.
宝箱上出现发光的字  上面写着
Glowing letters appear on the chest that read,
"如果你不想被夹死
"If squashed to death you wish not to be,
那就高歌圣威特·瓦茨拉夫和他的胜利"
sing of Svaty Vaclav and his victory."
-谁是圣威特·瓦茨拉夫  -墙越来越近了
- Who the hell is Svaty Vaclav? - Walls are getting closer.
我得赶紧想着开心的地方
Oh, boy, happy place, happy place.
通常有病的人要靠想着开心的地方转移注意力
等等  圣威特·瓦茨拉夫是波西米亚的君主
Wait, Svaty Vaclav was the Duke of Bohemia.
你还有十秒钟就要被夹成肉酱了
You're ten seconds away from getting crushed!
九  八...
Nine, eight...
我们该怎么办
What are we supposed to do?
-七  六  -等下  等下
- ...seven, six... - Wait, wait.
圣威特·瓦茨拉夫就是受人喜爱的
Svaty Vaclav is better known as Good King Wenceslas
维多利亚时代圣诞颂歌里的仁君温瑟拉
from the beloved Victorian Christmas carol.
从来没听说过
Never heard of it.
肯定就那首圣诞颂歌不是犹太人写的
Must be the one Christmas song not written by a Jewish guy.
三  二...
...three, two...
快唱那首该死的颂歌
Somebody sing the damn song!
* 是日圣徒节 *
* Good King Wenceslas looked out *
* 贤君帘外望 *
* On the feast of Stephen *
* 积雪覆大地 *
* When the snow lay 'round about *
* 松脆且平旷 *
* Deep and crisp and even *
墙越来越近啦
The walls are getting slower.
* 是夜月皎皎 *
* Brightly shone the moon that night *
* 寒霜亦凄凄 *
* Though the frost was cru-el *
* 但见褴褛者 *
* When a poor man came in sight *
* 拾薪不停息 *
* Gath'ring winter fu-el *
墙壁停下了  你们安全了
The walls stop! You're safe!
你可真牛  谢尔顿
That was amazing, Sheldon.
-你怎么会唱这个  -很简单
- How did you know that? - It was simple.
我将一个关于波西米亚的知名历史事件
I combined a well-known, historical fact
与我对外祖父母的记忆结合在一起
about Bohemia with the memory of my grandparents,
那时候外公和外婆  唱着圣诞颂歌
Mee-Maw and Pop-Pop, singing Christmas carols
而我在壁炉前尝试用乐高来制造
while I sat in front of the fire and tried to build
一个高能粒子加速器
a high-energy particle accelerator out of Legos.
继续我们的任务吧
Okay, continuing our quest.
等一下
W-W-Wait.
还有四段没唱呢
There's still four more verses.
总不能唱个开头没结尾吧
You don't sing a song and not finish it.
* 嗟尔侍者来 *
* Hither, page, and stand by me *
* 务必据实语 *
* If thou know'st it telling ,*
* 彼处何许人 *
* Yonder peasant, who is he? *
* 此人何所居 *
* Where and what his dwelling? *
* 是夜月皎皎  寒霜亦凄... *
* Brightly shone the moon that night, though the frost...*
看来他进展不错啊
It Looks like he's doing pretty good.
那是当然了
Of course he is.
那姑娘刚被男朋友甩了
Look, that girl just got dumped by her boyfriend.
满心愤怒  又醉得烂醉
She's angry, she's drunk,
最爱的电影还是印度电影《贫民窟的百万富翁》
and her favorite movie is Slumdog Millionaire. I mean...
必须手到擒来啊
That is some low-hanging fruit.
他回来了
Oh, here he comes.
-怎么样啊  -一切顺利
- So, how'd it go? - Great.
我请她喝了几杯酒
I bought her a couple of drinks,
她就把邮箱地址给我了
and she gave me her E-mail address.
杰妮芙@就算男人死光了只剩你都不要.废柴
"Jennifer@not-even-if-you-were- the-last-guy-on-earth.loser""
什么
What?
真遗憾  拉杰
I'm sorry, Raj.
我怎么就找不到我的佳人呢
Why can't I find someone?
我智商高  工作好
I'm smart, I've got a cool job,
天生古铜的肤色说明
and my naturally bronzed complexion means
别人穿了难看的芥末黄  我也能穿得帅气
I can pull off mustard yellow in a way most guys can't.
亲爱的  不怪你  是她们脑子有病
Oh, honey, it's not you, it's them.
不是的
No, it's not.
她太漂亮了  我高攀不上
She was too beautiful for me.
-你怎么会说这种话  -是真的
- Why would you say that? - It's true.
我总是迷恋自己得不到的姑娘
I'm always attracted to women I can't have.
我老是这样
I do it all the time.
我以前对你们两个就是啊
I did the same thing with the two of you.
她们两个
The two of them?
我不太明白
I don't understand.
曾经有段时间我暗恋过佩妮
Well, uh, there was a time when I had a thing for Penny,
而且当时我以为她也喜欢我
and I thought she was into me, too,
因为有一次她喝醉后脱光
because she got drunk and naked
跟我爬上了床
and climbed into bed with me.
但很显然是我自作多情了
But apparently I misread those signals.
你也喜欢过伯纳黛特啊
And you liked Bernadette also?
那是在佩妮之前
That was before Penny.
我自己定了个规矩  一次只能
I make it a rule to only fall for
爱上一位好朋友的女朋友
one of my friends' girlfriends at a time.
这方面我挺传统的
I'm very old-fashioned that way.
也就是说你曾经
So at, uh, some point,
也喜欢过我了吧
you probably had a thing for me, too.
那倒没有
No, not really.
拜托  拉杰  一点都没有吗
Oh, come on, Raj, not even a little bit?
反正我想不起来这样过
Not that I can think of.
给老娘仔细想
Think harder.
没有
Nope.
我的心会跟着心的感觉走吧
I guess the heart wants what the heart wants.
而她不是我的菜
Or in this case, doesn't.
完全没兴趣
I mean, at all.
看我干嘛
What?
* 但能济贫士 *
* Ye who now will bless the poor *
* 赐福自返还 *
* Shall yourselves find blessing *
完啦
Done?
你想说的唱完赞叹词应该是"棒啊"
I think the word you're looking for is "bravo."
现在你们离开那个房间  发现自己
Okay, you leave the room and find yourself
来到一个里面有融化的雪人的池子面前
standing before a pool of melted snowmen.
融化的雪人
Melted snowmen?
水里有雪人五官的胡萝卜和煤块吗
Are there carrots and lumps of coal in the water?
不知道  有差别吗
I don't know. What's the difference?
这是个幻想游戏  莱纳德
It's a game of the imagination, Leonard.
-给我好好描述画面  -好吧
- Paint a picture. - Fine.
你离开那个房间  发现自己
You leave the room and find yourself
来到一个里面有融化的雪人的池子面前
standing before a pool of melted snowmen.
水里尽是胡萝卜和煤块
There are carrots and lumps of coal in the water.
那雪人的大帽子和烟斗上哪了呢
Do we know what happened to the top hats and the corncob pipes?
你也看见它们在水里了
You see those, too.
真是身临其境呀
Oh, it's like I'm really there.
自从我的治疗师换了我的焦虑症药
I gotta tell you, this-this is the most holiday fun I've had
而且我也再也不在乎我的血便后
since my therapist changed my anxiety medication
我不得不说  这是我最开心的过节了
and I stopped caring about the blood in my stool.
好故事
Good story.
你喝什么呢
What are you drinking there?
蛋奶酒吗
Little eggnog?
是的
Yes.
怎么了  不行吗
What, is there a problem?
看你喝圣诞饮品挺好的
No, it's nice to see you enjoying a holiday beverage.
很有节日氛围
Pretty Christmasy.
蛋奶酒什么时候成圣诞专属了
Since when is eggnog a Christmas drink?
一年四季都有鸡蛋生产
Eggs are available all year 'round.
大家都知道我爱在泳池边喝这个
I've been known to enjoy this poolside.
拜托  谢尔顿
Come on, Sheldon.
你知道每一个圣诞故事  和颂歌
You know all the Christmas stories, and the carols,
现在还喝出了个蛋奶酒小胡子
you've got an eggnog mustache going on there.
承认吧
Just admit it.
你挺喜欢圣诞的
You're getting a little Yuletide spirit.
别傻了
Oh, don't be silly.
圣诞节只不过是装饰品工业编出来骗钱的
Christmas is a bunch of baloney created by the tinsel industry.
对你来说有什么要紧的啊
Why is this so important to you?
坦白说  因为我小时候的圣诞节都过得很糟
Honestly, because I had enough crappy Christmases as a kid
现在不想你再扫我的兴了
and I'm tired of you sucking the joy out of them now.
怎么过得不好了
What was so bad about them?
我家人都是疯子学术家
I grew up in a house full of crazy academics.
我们小孩不给圣诞老人留牛奶和饼干
Instead of leaving Santa milk and cookies,
而是得留给他一份研究报告
we had to leave him a research paper.
而第二天早晨  你会知道圣诞老人来过
And in the morning, you could tell he'd been there
因为你留的报告都评好分了
because the paper would be graded.
怪不得你这么喜欢圣诞节
No wonder you love Christmas.
听起来真是太酷了
That sounds amazing.
一点也不酷
It wasn't amazing.
我曾连续四年得了C-
I got a C-minus four years in a row.
我知道你的水平
Yeah, I'm familiar with your work.
C-都算送了你大礼了
C-minus was your gift.
艾米  真是对不起
Amy, I'm really sorry.
我不是故意让你难过的
I didn't mean to upset you.
没事
It's fine.
我已经习惯被男生无视了
I'm used to being the girl who never gets looked at twice.
直到22岁  我才等到我的初吻
I didn't have my first kiss till I was 22,
那人亲我是因为我拿他的胰岛素要挟
and the guy only did it so I'd give him back his insulin.
有时候  胰腺会跟着胰腺的感觉走
Sometimes the pancreas wants what the pancreas wants.
算了
Forget it.
我没指望你们能明白
I don't expect you guys to understand.
我明白
I understand.
七年级我玩"转瓶子"游戏时
In seventh grade, I played Spin the Bottle
瓶子指向谁 转的人就去亲对方
瓶子指向了爱林娜·香卡
and it landed on Alina Shankar.
她说如果我敢靠近她
She said if I came near her,
她就敲碎瓶子捅我
she would break the bottle and cut me.
你觉得这样算悲催吗
You think that's bad?
大学时  我在兄弟会派对上喝到不省人事
In college, I passed out at a frat party
醒来时发现衣服没少  反而更多了
and woke up with more clothes on.
有时候我感觉太孤单
Sometimes I get so lonely,
我会坐在左手上直到左手麻木
I sit on my left hand until it goes numb,
然后用右手握住
then I put it in my right hand
假装是别人在握住我的手
and pretend I'm holding hands with another person.
我也会这么做
I do that, too.
有时候左手想伸伸禄山之爪
Sometimes the left hand tries to cop a feel.
我也任它随便摸
And I let it.
能和了解孤单的人聊天
It's kind of nice to talk to someone who understands
感觉真是太好了
what it feels like to be alone.
是吧
It is, isn't it?
但你现在不再孤单了
But you're not alone anymore.
-你有谢尔顿  -是的
- Now you've got Sheldon. - I do.
别担心  终有一天你也会有佳人相伴的
And don't worry, someday you'll have somebody, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
她只要有你一半美丽聪慧  我就心满意足了
I hope she's half as lovely and amazing as you are.
谢谢你  拉杰什
Thank you, Rajesh.
他对我动心了  我满意了  撤
He wants me, I'm good. We can go now.
我靠
Damn it.
怎么了
What?
现在我知道她不喜欢我
Now that I know she doesn't like me,
我好像有点喜欢她了
I'm kind of into her.
好了
All right.
我想我破解了密码  可以放下吊桥了
I think I cracked the code to lower the drawbridge.
太好了  开始吧
Great. Let's do it.
吊桥正在缓缓放下
The drawbridge is lowering.
我的腕管综合症发作了
My carpal tunnel's acting up.
痛也得坚持
Play through the pain!
成功了  吊桥放下了
You did it! The drawbridge is down.
你们跨过峡谷
You cross the chasm
来到一间小小的地牢
and find yourself in a small dungeon room.
在墙角  是被铁链锁住
And in the corner, chained to the wall,
被打到浑身鲜血的圣诞老人
you see a bloodied and beaten Santa Claus.
他说  "呵  呵  救命"
He says, "Ho, ho, help me."
太棒了  我们找到了圣诞老人
Yes, we found Santa!
圣诞节被拯救了
Christmas is saved!
千万别告诉我妈我说过这句话[犹太人不过圣诞]
Don't ever tell my mother I said that.
我取出万能钥匙
I take out my skeleton key
跑向圣诞老人给他解开铁链
and run to Santa to unchain him.
但我抢先向斯图尔特和霍华德施了麻痹咒
But first, I cast a spell of paralysis on Stuart and Howard.
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
你不能说话  你已经被我麻痹了
You can't talk; you're paralyzed.
我来到圣诞老人的大肥脸跟前说
I get right up in Santa's big, fat face and say...
瞧瞧瞧
Well, well, well,
乐呵呵的圣诞老头儿  我们又见面了
Jolly old Saint Nick, we meet again.
Jolly Old Saint Nicholas是一首著名的圣诞歌
我相信上次我们聊天
Yeah, I believe the last time we spoke
还是在德州加尔维斯顿市的溪湾商场
was in the Baybrook Mall in Galveston, Texas,
我当时五岁  对吗
when I was five years old, isn't that right?
好吧
Uh, okay.
我妈硬把我拉去
My mother dragged me there
让我坐在你的大腿上
and she plopped me down on your lap
你问我圣诞节想要什么
and you asked me what I wanted for Christmas.
我告诉你  "我要我的外公"
And I told you "My Pop-Pop,"
因为那年我的外公去世了
because that was the year my grandfather died.
我想他  我想让他死而复生
I missed him and I wanted him back.
现在有点诡异  对吧
This is weird, right?
家里只有外公一个人
Pop-Pop was the only one in my family
鼓励我追求科学的真谛
who encouraged me to pursue science.
但你没让他起死回生  对吗
But you didn't bring him back, did you?
我得到的礼物是林肯积木
Instead, I got Lincoln Logs.
用林肯积木可以搭出很多有意思的东西
Well, you can build a lot of neat things out of Lincoln Logs,
但是搭不出外公
but Pop-Pop ain't one of 'em.
你现在竟然敢向我提出要求
And now you're here asking me for something--
要我救你
to save you.
抱歉了  圣诞老人先生
Well, sorry, Mr. Kringle,
今天不能让你如愿了
but today's not your day.
我要让你死在这里
I'm leaving you here to rot,
希望食人魔把你吃到尸骨无存
and I hope the ogres feast on your bones.
我拿起万能钥匙
I take the skeleton key,
扔进峡谷里
and I toss it into the chasm,
离开之前  我给了圣诞老人的
and on the way out, I give Santa
肥果冻肚皮闪电一踹
a swift kick in his bowl full of jelly!
bowl full of jelly  装满果冻的碗  是圣诞歌的歌词
形容圣诞老人的肚子
好吧
Okay.
沃罗威茨和斯图尔特被麻痹了  圣诞老人死了
So Wolowitz and Stuart are paralyzed, Santa's dead,
而我居然不和女友上床跑来玩这个
and I picked this over having sex with my girlfriend.
圣诞老人
Santa?
你好  谢尔顿
Oh, hello, Sheldon.
你应该在睡觉啊
You should be asleep.
那你就别在靴子上挂铃铛吵人睡觉啊
Well, then, you shouldn't have jingle bells on your boots.
我想跟你聊聊
I've been wanting to talk to you.
抱歉在你小时候  我让你失望了
I'm sorry I disappointed you when you were a little boy.
我能施展魔法做到不少事
I-I can do a lot of magical things,
但遗憾的是
but unfortunately
我没有能力让你的外公死而复生
bringing your Pop-Pop back isn't one of them.
我明白
I understand.
但我有特别的礼物送给你
But I-I do have something special for you.
闭上眼
Close your eyes.
希望是火车
Oh, I hope it's a train.
比火车要好
Oh, it's better than a train.
两辆火车吗
Two trains?
更好
Better.
我要有三辆火车啦
I'm getting three trains.
好了  睁眼吧
Okay, open 'em.
这是回敬你把我留在地牢
This is for leaving me in the dungeon
让食人魔给生吞活剥了
to be eaten alive by ogres!
等等  别激动
Wait, uh, uh, hang on.
容我解释下
I-In my defense...
呵呵呵  你个大傻帽
Ho, ho, ho, ya big dork!